[
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "home",
        "instructions": "Welcome to Emmet-Type!",
        "question": "1. Select a topic to learn.\n2. Type in the abbreviation in the text box below.\n3. Press the tab key to enter your answer.\n4. Press <-- and --> to cycle through the problems.\n5. Press \"?\" to show hints.",
        "answer": ["Select a topic to start learning!"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "tags",
        "instructions": "Type the tag name and press tab.",
        "question": "<div></div>",
        "answer": ["div"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "tags",
        "instructions": "Type the tag name and press tab.",
        "question": "<p></p>",
        "answer": ["p"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "tags",
        "instructions": "Type the tag name and press tab.",
        "question": "<h1></h1>",
        "answer": ["h1"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "child",
        "instructions": "Child = tag>tag",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<div></div>\n</div>",
        "answer": ["div>div"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "child",
        "instructions": "Child = tag>tag",
        "question": "<nav>\n\t<ul>\n\t\t<li></li>\n\t</ul>\n</nav>",
        "answer": ["nav>ul>li"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "siblings",
        "instructions": "Siblings = tag+tag",
        "question": "<div></div>\n<div></div>",
        "answer": ["div+div", "div*2"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "siblings",
        "instructions": "Siblings = tag+tag",
        "question": "<p></p>\n<p></p>",
        "answer": ["p+p", "p*2"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "siblings",
        "instructions": "Siblings = tag+tag",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<p></p>\n\t<p></p>\n</div>",
        "answer": ["div>p+p", "div>p*2"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "siblings",
        "instructions": "Siblings = tag+tag",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li+li+li", "ul>li*3"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "climb",
        "instructions": "Use ^ to climb up.\nEx.: outerTag>childTag^(to climb out)outerTag>childTag\nRemember to press \"?\" for hints!",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<p></p>\n</div>\n<div>\n\t<p></p>\n</div>",
        "answer": ["div>p^div>p", "div*2>p"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "climb",
        "instructions": "Use ^ to climb up.\nEx.: outerTag>childTag^(to climb out)outerTag>childTag\nRemember to press \"?\" for hints!",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<p><span></span></p>\n\t<p><span></span></p>\n</div>",
        "answer": ["div>p>span^p>span"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "climb",
        "instructions": "Use ^ to climb up.\nEx.: outerTag>childTag^(to climb out)outerTag>childTag\nRemember to press \"?\" for hints!",
        "question": "<section>\n\t<div>\n\t\t<p><span></span></p>\n\t\t<p><span></span></p>\n\t</div>\n\t<blockquote></blockquote>\n</section>",
        "answer": ["section>div>p>span^p>span^^blockquote"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "group",
        "instructions": "Use () to group together a set of tags.\nRemember to press \"?\" for hints!",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<header>\n\t\t<ul>\n\t\t\t<li><a href=\"\"></a></li>\n\t\t\t<li><a href=\"\"></a></li>\n\t\t</ul>\n\t</header>\n\t<footer>\n\t\t<p></p>\n\t</footer>\n</div>",
        "answer": ["div>(header>ul>li*2>a)+footer>p"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "group",
        "instructions": "Use () to group together a set of tags.\nRemember to press \"?\" for hints!",
        "question": "<div>\n\t<dl>\n\t\t<dt></dt>\n\t\t<dd></dd>\n\t\t<dt></dt>\n\t\t<dd></dd>\n\t\t<dt></dt>\n\t\t<dd></dd>\n\t</dl>\n</div>\n<footer>\n\t<p></p>\n</footer>",
        "answer": ["(div>dl>(dt+dd)*3)+footer>p"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "multiplication",
        "instructions": "Multiplication = tag*number.",
        "question": "<div></div>\n<div></div>\n<div></div>\n<div></div>\n<div></div>",
        "answer": ["div*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "multiplication",
        "instructions": "Multiplication = tag*number.",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "multiplication",
        "instructions": "Multiplication = tag*number.",
        "question": "<section>\n\t<h1></h1>\n\t<p></p>\n\t<p></p>\n\t<p></p>\n</section>",
        "answer": ["section>h1+p*3"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "multiplication",
        "instructions": "Multiplication = tag*number.",
        "question": "<nav>\n\t<div><a href=\"\"></a></div>\n\t<div><a href=\"\"></a></div>\n\t<div><a href=\"\"></a></div>\n\t<div><a href=\"\"></a></div>\n\t<div><a href=\"\"></a></div>\n</nav>",
        "answer": ["nav>div*5>a"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "numbering",
        "instructions": "Numbering = $\nPlace a $ where you want your numbers to appear\nThen multiply (*) by the desired number.",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li class=\"item1\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item2\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item3\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item4\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item5\"></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li.item$*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "numbering",
        "instructions": "Numbering = $\nPlace a $ where you want your numbers to appear\nThen multiply (*) by the desired number.",
        "question": "<h1 title=\"item1\">Header 1</h1>\n<h2 title=\"item2\">Header 2</h2>\n<h3 title=\"item3\">Header 3</h3>",
        "answer": ["h$[title=item$]{Header $}*3"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "numbering",
        "instructions": "Numbering = $\n$$$ = 001, 002, etc.",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li class=\"item001\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item002\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item003\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item004\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item005\"></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li.item$$$*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "numbering",
        "instructions": "Set the starting number = $@, then multiply\nEx.: tag.item$@*starting-number",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li class=\"item3\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item4\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item5\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item6\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item7\"></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li.item$@3*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "numbering",
        "instructions": "Descending numbers = $@-*starting-number\n",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li class=\"item5\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item4\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item3\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item2\"></li>\n\t<li class=\"item1\"></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li.item$@-*5"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "class-id",
        "instructions": "Class = .class-name\nID = #id-name\n(Ex.: tag.class-name#id-name)",
        "question": "<div id=\"header\"></div>",
        "answer": ["div#header", "#header"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "class-id",
        "instructions": "Class = .class-name\nID = #id-name\n(Ex.: tag.class-name#id-name)",
        "question": "<div class=\"title\"></div>",
        "answer": ["div.title", ".title"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "class-id",
        "instructions": "Class = .class-name\nID = #id-name\n(Ex.: tag.class-name#id-name)",
        "question": "<form id=\"search\" class=\"wide\"></form>",
        "answer": ["form#search.wide"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "class-id",
        "instructions": "Class = .class-name\nID = #id-name\n(Ex.: tag.class-name#id-name)",
        "question": "<p class=\"class1 class2 class3\"></p>",
        "answer": ["p.class1.class2.class3"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "custom-attr",
        "instructions": "Custom attributes = any attribute that is NOT .class or #id.\nEx.: tag[custom-attr-name=\"Custom attribute value\"",
        "question": "<p title=\"Hello world\"></p>",
        "answer": ["p[title=\"Hello world\"]"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "custom-attr",
        "instructions": "Custom attributes = any attribute that is NOT .class or #id.\nEx.: tag[custom-attr-name=\"Custom attribute value\"",
        "question": "<td rowspan=\"2\" colspan=\"3\" title=\"\"></td>",
        "answer": ["td[rowspan=2 colspan=3 title]"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "custom-attr",
        "instructions": "Custom attributes = any attribute that is NOT .class or #id.\nEx.: tag[custom-attr-name=\"Custom attribute value\"",
        "question": "<div a=\"value1\" b=\"value2\"></div>",
        "answer": ["[a='value1' b=\"value2\"]"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "text",
        "instructions": "Text = {your text here}",
        "question": "<a href=\"\">Click me</a>",
        "answer": ["a{Click me}"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "text",
        "instructions": "Text = {your text here}",
        "question": "<p>Click <a href=\"\">here</a> to continue</p>",
        "answer": ["p>{Click }+a{here}+{ to continue}"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "implicit",
        "instructions": "Implicit tags = just type in the .class or #id,\nand emmet will know the tag based on the context.",
        "question": "<div class=\"class\"></div>",
        "answer": [".class"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "implicit",
        "instructions": "Implicit tags = just type in the .class or #id,\nand emmet will know the tag based on the context.",
        "question": "<em><span class=\"class\"></span></em>",
        "answer": ["em>.class"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "implicit",
        "instructions": "Implicit tags = just type in the .class or #id,\nand emmet will know the tag based on the context.",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li class=\"class\"></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>.class"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "implicit",
        "instructions": "Implicit tags = just type in the .class or #id,\nand emmet will know the tag based on the context.",
        "question": "<table>\n\t<tr class=\"row\">\n\t\t<td class=\"col\"></td>\n\t</tr>\n</table>",
        "answer": ["table>.row>.col"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "practice",
        "instructions": "Practice what you've learned!",
        "question": "<ul>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n\t<li></li>\n</ul>",
        "answer": ["ul>li*5", "ul>li+li+li+li+li"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "practice",
        "instructions": "Practice what you've learned!",
        "question": "<section>\n\t<div>\n\t\t<p><span></span></p>\n\t\t<p><span></span></p>\n\t</div>\n\t<blockquote></blockquote>\n</section>",
        "answer": ["section>(div>p*2>span)+blockquote", "section>div>p>span^p>span^^blockquote", "section>div>p*2>span^^blockquote"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "practice",
        "instructions": "Practice what you've learned!",
        "question": "<p>Click <a href=\"\">here</a> to continue</p>",
        "answer": ["p>{Click }+a{here}+{ to continue}"]
    },
    {
        "level": "basic",
        "topic": "practice",
        "instructions": "Practice what you've learned!",
        "question": "<h1 title=\"item1\">Header 1</h1>\n<h2 title=\"item2\">Header 2</h2>\n<h3 title=\"item3\">Header 3</h3>",
        "answer": ["h$[title=item$]{Header $}*3"]
    }
]